<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.basket</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.basket.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer_name>KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">KDE gemeenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">KDE-gemenskapen</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Communityxx</developer_name>
  <name>Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxBasketxx</name>
  <summary>Notes and to-dos organizer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Organitzador de notes i tasques pendents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Organisator van notities en te-doens</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Antecknings- och uppgiftsorganisatör</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для впорядкування нотаток і завдань</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxNotes and to-dos organizerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>This application provides as many baskets as you wish, and you can drag and drop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquesta aplicació proporciona tantes cistelles com desitgeu, i les podeu arrossegar i deixar anar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Deze toepassing levert zoveel baskets als u wilt en u kunt slepen en loslaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Programmet tillhandahåller så många korgar som du vill, och du kan dra och släppa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ця програма створює довільну кількість кошиків, які ви можете перетягувати і скидати.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis application provides as many baskets as you wish, and you can drag and drop.xx</p>
    <p>Objects can be edited, copied, dragged... So, you can arrange them as you want !</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Els objectes es poden editar, copiar, arrossegar... És a dir, els podeu organitzar com vulgueu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Objecten kunnen bewerkt, gekopieerd, versleept worden... U kunt ze dus arrangeren zoals u wilt!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Objekt kan redigeras, kopieras, dras, ... Så du kan arrangera dem som du vill.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Об'єкти можна редагувати, копіювати, перетягувати… Отже, ви можете впорядкувати їх так, як вам заманеться!</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxObjects can be edited, copied, dragged... So, you can arrange them as you want !xx</p>
    <p>It allows to arrange notes, track to-dos and much more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Permet organitzar notes, seguir tasques pendents i molt més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het biedt het arrangeren van notities, het volgen van te-doens en veel meer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Den gör det möjligt att arrangera anteckningar, följa uppgifter, med mera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма уможливлює упорядкування нотаток, стеження за завданнями та виконання багатьох інших завдань.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt allows to arrange notes, track to-dos and much more.xx</p>
  </description>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
  </categories>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
