<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.basket</id>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">org.kde.basket.desktop</launchable>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0-or-later</project_license>
  <developer_name>KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ca-valencia">La comunitat KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="cs">Komunita KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="da">KDE-fællesskabet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="de">KDE-Gemeinschaft</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="en-GB">KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="es">Comunidad KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="et">KDE kogukond</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="eu">KDE komunitatea</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fi">KDE-yhteisö</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="fr">Communauté KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ia">Communitate de KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="id">Komunitas KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="it">Comunità KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ka">KDE Community</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ko">KDE 커뮤니티</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nl">KDE-gemeenschap</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="nn">KDE-fellesskapet</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pl">Społeczność KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt">Comunidade do KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="pt-BR">Comunidade KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="ru">Сообщество KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sk">KDE komunita</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sl">Skupnost KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="sv">KDE-gemenskapen</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="tr">KDE Topluluğu</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="uk">Спільнота KDE</developer_name>
  <developer_name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Communityxx</developer_name>
  <name>Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">კალათა</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="nn">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Koszyk</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Basket</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxBasketxx</name>
  <summary>Notes and to-dos organizer</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Organitzador de notes i tasques pendents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Organitzador de notes i tasques pendents</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Shromažďování poznámek a úkolů</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">Notes and to-dos organiser</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Organizador de notas y tareas pendientes</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Märkmete ja ülesannete korraldaja</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">Oharren eta zereginen antolatzailea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">Muistiinpano- ja tehtäväjärjestäjä</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Notes et organisateur de tâches à faire</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Organisator de Notas e Agenda</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Pengelola catatan dan wacana</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Gestore di note e cose da fare</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">შენიშვნების და განაწესის ორგანიზატორი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">메모와 할 일 관리 도구</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">Organisator van notities en te-doens</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nn">Notat- og gjeremålorganisering</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Organizer notatek i zadań</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Organizador de notas e tarefas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Organizador de notas e tarefas</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Organizator zabeležk in nalog</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Antecknings- och uppgiftsorganisatör</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">Notlar ve yapılacaklar düzenleyicisi</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Програма для впорядкування нотаток і завдань</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxNotes and to-dos organizerxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>This application provides as many baskets as you wish, and you can drag and drop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Aquesta aplicació proporciona tantes cistelles com desitgeu, i les podeu arrossegar i deixar anar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Esta aplicació proporciona tantes cistelles com voleu, i les podeu arrossegar i deixar anar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Tato aplikace poskytuje kolik košíků chcete a můžete je různě přesunovat.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">This application provides as many baskets as you wish, and you can drag and drop.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Esta aplicación proporciona todas las cestas que necesite, donde puede arrastrar y soltar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">See rakendus pakub nii palju korve, kui vähegi vaja, ning siin saab ka lohistada.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Aplikazio honek nahi adina saski hornitzen ditu, eta arrastatu eta jaregin daiteke.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Sovellus tarjoaa niin monta koria kuin haluat, ja se tukee vetämistä ja pudottamista.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cette application fournit autant de paniers que vous désirez et que vous pouvez utiliser par glisser/déposer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Iste application provide omne le panieros que on vole, e tu pote traher e deponer. </p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Aplikasi ini menyediakan keranjang sebanyak yang kamu inginkan, dan kamu bisa melakukan seret dan taruh.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Questa applicazione ti mette a disposizione tutti i cesti che vuoi, e puoi trascinarvi del contenuto.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">이 프로그램은 여러 개의 바구니를 만들어서 드래그 앤 드롭할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Deze toepassing levert zoveel baskets als u wilt en u kunt slepen en loslaten.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Program pozwala na posiadanie tylu koszyków ile chcesz, a nawet na przeciąganie i upuszczanie.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Esta aplicação oferece tantos cestos quantos desejar, podendo depois arrastar e largar conteúdos neles.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Ta aplikacija ponuja toliko košar, kot želite, lahko jih povlečete in spuščate.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Programmet tillhandahåller så många korgar som du vill, och du kan dra och släppa.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Bu uygulama, içine sürükleyip bırakabileceğiniz istediğiniz sayıda sepet sunar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Ця програма створює довільну кількість кошиків, які ви можете перетягувати і скидати.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxThis application provides as many baskets as you wish, and you can drag and drop.xx</p>
    <p>Objects can be edited, copied, dragged... So, you can arrange them as you want !</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Els objectes es poden editar, copiar, arrossegar... És a dir, els podeu organitzar com vulgueu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Els objectes es poden editar, copiar, arrossegar... És a dir, els podeu organitzar com vulgueu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Objects can be edited, copied, dragged... So, you can arrange them as you want !</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Puede editar objetos, copiarlos, arrastrarlos... De este modo, puede organizarlos como desee.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Objekte saad muuta, kopeerida, lohistada ... Sõnaga, kõike saab korraldada just oma maitse järgi!</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Objektuak editatu, kopiatu, arrastatu... daitezke, nahi duzun bezala antolatu ditzakezu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kohteita voi muokata, kopioida, vetää… Voit siis järjestää niitä miten haluat!</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Les objets peuvent être modifiés, copiés, glissés... Par conséquent, vous pouvez les arranger comme vous le souhaitez !</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Objectos pote esser modificate, copiate e trahite... assi que tu pote disponer los como tu vole!</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Objek bisa diedit, disalin, diseret ... Jadi, kamu bisa mengaturnya sesuai keinginanmu!</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Gli oggetti possono essere modificati, copiati, trascinati... Puoi quindi organizzarli come preferisci!</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">객체는 자유롭게 편집, 복사, 드래그하여 원하는 대로 배치할 수 있습니다!</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Objecten kunnen bewerkt, gekopieerd, versleept worden... U kunt ze dus arrangeren zoals u wilt!</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Obiekty można edytować, kopiować, przeciągać... Tak więc możesz je ułożyć tak, jak chcesz !</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Os objectos poderão ser editados, copiados, arrastados... Por isso, pode organizá-los como desejar !</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Predmete lahko urejate, kopirate, vlečete ... Torej jih lahko uredite kot želite!</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Objekt kan redigeras, kopieras, dras, ... Så du kan arrangera dem som du vill.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Nesneler düzenlenebilir, kopyalanabilir, sürüklenebilir... İstediğiniz gibi düzenleyibilirsiniz!</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Об'єкти можна редагувати, копіювати, перетягувати… Отже, ви можете впорядкувати їх так, як вам заманеться!</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxObjects can be edited, copied, dragged... So, you can arrange them as you want !xx</p>
    <p>It allows to arrange notes, track to-dos and much more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Permet organitzar notes, seguir tasques pendents i molt més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Permet organitzar notes, seguir tasques pendents i molt més.</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Umožňuje organizovat poznámky, sledovat úlohy a spoustu dalšího.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">It allows to arrange notes, track to-dos and much more.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Permite organizar notas y hacer seguimiento de tareas pendientes, entre otras cosas.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">See võimaldab korraldada märkmeid, hoida silma peal ülesannetel ja veel palju muud.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Oharrak antolatzeko, zereginen jarraipena egiteko eta askoz gehiagorako aukera eskaintzen du.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Muistiinpanoja voi järjestää, tehtävien etenemistä seurata ja paljon muuta.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Cela vous permet d'arranger vos notes et de suivre vos tâches à faire et bien d'autres choses.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Il permitte disponer notas, traciar agenda de cosas de facer e plus alteres.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Yang memungkinkan untuk mengatur catatan, melacak wacana dan banyak lagi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Ti permette di organizzare note, tenere traccia delle cose da fare, e altro ancora.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">საშუალებას გაძლევთ, დალაგოთ შენიშვნები, ყურადღება ადევნოთ განაწესს და ბევრი სხვა.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">메모 관리, 할 일 추적 등을 할 수 있습니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Het biedt het arrangeren van notities, het volgen van te-doens en veel meer.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Umożliwia porządkowanie notatek, zadań i wiele więcej.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Permite organizar as notas, acompanhar as tarefas e muito mais.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Omogoča urejanje zabeležk, nalog in veliko več.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Den gör det möjligt att arrangera anteckningar, följa uppgifter, med mera.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Notları, yapılacakları ve çok daha fazlasını izlemenize olanak verir.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Програма уможливлює упорядкування нотаток, стеження за завданнями та виконання багатьох інших завдань.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxIt allows to arrange notes, track to-dos and much more.xx</p>
  </description>
  <categories>
    <category>Office</category>
  </categories>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
</component>
